<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quiz for Kids</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="count_0">0</string>
    <string name="count_1">1</string>
    <string name="count_2">2</string>
    <string name="count_3">3</string>
    <string name="count_4">4</string>
    <string name="count_5">5</string>
    <string name="count_6">6</string>
    <string name="count_7">7</string>
    <string name="count_8">8</string>
    <string name="count_9">9</string>
    <string name="count_10">10</string>
    <string name="count_11">11</string>
    <string name="count_12">12</string>
    <string name="count_13">13</string>
    <string name="count_14">14</string>
    <string name="count_15">15</string>
    <string name="count_16">16</string>
    <string name="count_17">17</string>
    <string name="count_18">18</string>
    <string name="count_19">19</string>
    <string name="count_20">20</string>
    <string name="level">Level:</string>
    <string name="level_p">To complete a level, score 20 points.</string>
    <string name="level1">Level 1</string>
    <string name="level_one">Select the largest number.</string>
    <string name="level_end">Level passed!</string>
    <string name="level_one_end">"   The Arabic word for \"digit\" means \"zero\". Later, this word was used to refer to any digit."</string>
    <string name="text_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="level_two">Select the largest Roman number.</string>
    <string name="level2">Level 2</string>
    <string name="level_two_end">"   Roman numerals were used in the Roman Empire. Nowadays, they are used to refer to centuries, months. They can be seen on the watch faces.\n   And it is also interesting that there is no \"zero\" in Roman numerals."</string>
    <string name="level_three">Guess the hidden numbers in the pictures and select the largest one.</string>
    <string name="level3">Level 3</string>
    <string name="level_three_end">"   The number eight is considered the number of perfection, balance and cosmic order. It is associated with infinity, and is also a symbol of love and friendship."</string>
    <string name="level_four">Guess the hidden numbers in the pictures and select the even one.</string>
    <string name="level4">Level 4</string>
    <string name="level_four_end">"   Any number divisible by two without a remainder is considered an even number."</string>
    <string name="level_five">What can I eat?</string>
    <string name="level5">Level 5</string>
    <string name="level_five_end">"   In some countries, they are happy to eat what is considered inedible in others. For example, in France, frog legs are a delicacy."</string>
    <string name="level_six">Select something that, from a culinary point of view, is a fruit or berry.</string>
    <string name="level6">Level 6</string>
    <string name="level_six_end">"   Is tomato a vegetable or a fruit?\n   Europeans call fruits soft juicy fruits. This is the only reason why you can call a tomato a fruit plant.\n   In Russia, they are skeptical about this: we do not add tomatoes to sweet dishes, do not pour ice cream juice on them, do not treat children with it as sweets. Therefore, for our country, tomato is only a vegetable."</string>
    <string name="level_seven">Which is the first month of the year?</string>
    <string name="level7">Level 7</string>
    <string name="level_seven_end">"   Previously, the New Year was celebrated on 14, January. The Old New Year is an additional holiday that resulted from a change in the chronology."</string>
    <string name="level_eight">Choose a live one.</string>
    <string name="level8">Level 8</string>
    <string name="level_eight_end">"   All animate objects in the world are created by nature. These are plants, animals, fungi, and bacteria. Inanimate nature includes: sun, air, water, mountains, rocks, sand, sky, stars. In the same way, everything that is made by human hands belongs to the inanimate objects.</string>
    <string name="level9">Level 9</string>
    <string name="level_nine">Who lives on the farm?</string>
    <string name="level_nine_end">"   Scientists suggest that the goat was one of the first animals to be domisticated."</string>
    <string name="level10">Level 10</string>
    <string name="level_ten">Who is a predator here?</string>
    <string name="level_ten_end">"   Bears are considered to be one of the most dangerous predators on Earth. They live in almost every corner of the globe, including the North Pole."</string>
</resources>